Preliminary Guide to the Gelman Library, Slavic, East European, and Asian Reading Room records, 1962-1995 RG0132
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office files, 1962-1995; RG0132 Series 2; 36 Linear feet
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowships, Chinese and Russian programs, 10/1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    For 1971-1972, awarded 02/1971
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Proposal For continuation of NDEA Center, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    For 1971-1972, submitted 01/1971
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: East Asian Studies, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowships, Russian and Chinese, 10/1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    For 1972-1973
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Summer, East Asian, Chinese/Japanese, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    denied 10/1972
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Int. Studies Center, Soviet Union and East Europe, 12/1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    For 1973-1974
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Int. Studies Center, East Asia, 12/1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowships, Russian, Chinese/Japanese, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    For 1974-1975, denied 07/08/1974
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowships, East Asia and Soviet Union, 03/1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    For 1976-1977, denied 04/1976
  - Foreign Curriculum Consultant:Watanabe, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Department of HEW: Request for Japanese curriculum consultant for 1972-1973, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    denied 02/03/1972
  - National Defense Education Act, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    memos
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    final reports
  - Teacher Improvement Training Project, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Office of Education: Poole Application, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - OE Educational Personnel Development, 02/1969-05/1969 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - National Defense Education Act, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 01/22/1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Letters to Nihei
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 04/22/1985 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Yash. Torii, Keio University
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Summery prepared by Stewart
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Questionnaire Guide - US-Japan Symposium
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Goals and Procedures
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 02/16/1984-02/17/1984 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    List of Participants
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 02/16/1984-02/17/1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    American Contributions
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    Stewart - Thailand trip report
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    Stewart - Indonesian trip report
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    Stewart - Analytical Framework
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    Nihei - Thailand Trip Report
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    Industrialization Policy of Indonesia/Nihei
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    Nihei - Analytical Framework
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    Nihei Indonesian Trip Report
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    "Comparative Study of Japanese and American firms" form
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    Chapter 01/Stewart
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    Chapter2:Local Environment for TeChapter Transfer
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
    Chapter2:Indonesia, Stewart
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    Chapter3:Thailand, Stewart
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    Chapter3:Indonesia, Stewart
  - U.S. Japan Technology Transfer from Japan: U.S., Thailand, and Indonesia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    Chapter: Conclusions and Recommendations/Stewart
  - Part-time faculty Files: Angel, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Baclawski, Joseph, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Banister, Judith, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Chi, Ping-Feng, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Dasbach, Anita, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Duke, Michael, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Dziak, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Evans, Jane, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Fu, Marilyn, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Griffin, Edward, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Grant, Stephen, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Hadley, Eleanor, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Halpern, Abraham, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Johnson, U. Alexis, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Kamerling, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Koike, Ikuo, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Macdonald, Donald, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Ploss, Sydney, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Poole, Peter A., undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Sargent, Peter, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Smith, Paul, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Socianu, Horia, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Part-time faculty Files: True, Phillip A., undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Warner, Edward, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Watanabe, Hajime, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Weber, Cynthia, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Part-time faculty Files: White, Nathan, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Wolfe, Thomas, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Part-time faculty Files: White, Ralph, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Willenz, Eric, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Worthy, Edmund, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Part-time faculty Files: Yano, Toru, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Full-time faculty Files: William R. Johnson, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Retired
  - Full-time faculty Files: William Lewis, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Vladimir Petrov, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Vladimir Petrov, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Shih, Chung-Wen [1/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Shih, Chung-Wen [2/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Shih, Chung-Wen [3/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Yin, Richard [1/2], undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Full-time faculty Files: Yin, Richard [2/2], undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Deceased Full-time Faculty Files: Sigur, Gaston J. [1/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Sigur, Gaston J. [2/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Sigur, Gaston J. [3/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Sigur, Gaston J. [4/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Michael, Franz [1/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Michael, Franz [2/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Michael, Franz [3/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Michael, Franz [4/4], undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Hinton, Harold [1/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Hinton, Harold [2/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Hinton, Harold [3/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Gyorgy, Angrew [1/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Gyorgy, Angrew [2/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Deceased Full-Time Faculty Files: Gyorgy, Angrew [3/3], undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 01/1990-02/1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 03/1990-06/1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 07/1990-12/1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 01/1991-03/1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 04/1991-07/1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 08/1991-10/1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 11/1991-12/1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 09/1989-12/1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 01/1990-05/1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 06/1990-12/1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 01/1991-06/1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 07/1991-12/1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 01/1995-07/1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 08/1995-09/1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing Memos, 01/1990-04/1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing Memos, 05/1990-12/1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Memos, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Faxes Sent, 10/1990-01/1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Faxes Sent, 01/1995-08/1995 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - New Kyunggi Agreement, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter Information, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Invitation to Ambassador Dubinin, 01/1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Hill Committee Report, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Overseas Agreements, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - CIA Conference: On Survey Research in the Successor States of the USSR, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Transcaucasian Course, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Enrollment Management, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Economics, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Kyunggi University Visitor, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Latvian Muskie Fellow, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Proposal for International Development Institute, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Dean East Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Eliot School of International Affairs Fellowship Selection, 03/94 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Eliot School of International Affairs Dean Search, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Eliot School of International Affairs: Ad-Hoc Committee on Non-Regular Eliot School of International Affairs Appoinments, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Council for the International Exchange of Scholars, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Japan-U.S. Friendship Comission, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Japanese Program Proposal, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Background for Japanese Studies Program, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Consortium History, 1965-1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Correspondence and outlines
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences Library, 1965-1983; Reports (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences Advisory Council, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Meeting Minutes
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences, 07/1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Survey of Research Centers and Institutes to Roderick French
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences Plan of Organization and First Charter, 1962-1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Related Correspondence
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Moving Memos & Floor Plans for move to Gelman Library
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences Executive Committee, 1973-1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences Faculty Meeting, 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Minutes
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Albright, David, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: An Zhaoru, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Baatar, Sosorbaramyn, 09/1990-04/1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Bae, Young-Shik, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Baidina, Oksana, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Blair, Sally Onesti, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Borhi, Laszlo, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Dere, Miklos, 09/1990-02/1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Dineva, Detelina, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Dubinin, Yuri, 01/1993-08/1993 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Duskin, Eric, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Fox, Martyna, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Garrett, Banning, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Glaser, Bonnie, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Gogsadze, George, 01/1994-05/1994 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Goodman, Melvin, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Gorin, Alexander, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Handleman, John, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Huang, Chun, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Kraus, Michael, 09/1990-05/1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Kim, Admiral Duk-Soo, 01/1994-06/1994 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Ko, General Myung Seung, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Liu, Liandi, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Liu, Ruiyi, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Lee, Kyeong Jae, 09/1991-08/1992 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Lu, Yimin, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Manguno, Joseph, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Menon, Rajan, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Michalek, Slavomir, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Miyata, Kenji, 01/1991-06/1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Moon, Jung-11, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Okada, Kunio, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Oh, Seung-Yeol, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Polisenka, Milada, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Popescu, Teodor Laurentiu, 04/1990-10/1990 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Shi, Gangzeng, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Shipovalnikov, Aleksei, 09/1990-11/1990 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Stewart-Hill, Anne, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Suzuki, Yuji, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Takita, Kenji, 04/1991-04/1992 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Tan Eng Bok, Georges, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Tax Choldin, Marianna, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Travers, Lee, 08/1990-08/1991 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Tsygankov, Andrei, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Vainshtein, Grigori, 09/1993-12/1993 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Wang, Jianwei, 11/1990-1/1991 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Wohlert, Torsten, 01/1992-05/1992 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Woo, Myung-sung, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Yoo, Chun-Beon, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Yoon, Young-Dae, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Zhang, Yifan, 01/1992-06/1992 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Zheng, Yongping, 09/1993-1/1994 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Research Fellow/Visiting Scholar: Zhou, Suhua, 09/1990-09/1991 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - International Research and Exchange Board Visitors, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - International Research and Exchange Board Visitors, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - International Research and Exchange Board Visitors, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Exchange Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Hannes Adomeit, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Evgenii Bazhanov, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Natalia Bazhanov, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Andrew Bennett, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Matthew Bonham, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Jeffrey Chechel, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Michele Crumley, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Natalia Geraskina, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: David Goldfrank, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Alexander Gordievsky, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Laura Guinn, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Natalia Kapitonova, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Mark Khrustlev, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Michele Kelemen, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Ruslan Kinebas, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Stanislav Kiselev, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Joshua Larson, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Andrei Leonov, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Martha Little, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Kelly Martek, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Vojtech Mastny, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Vladimir Matveyev, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Michael Mendelson, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Alexander Minialov, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Dmitrii Osipov, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: David Rich, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Phillip Rogers, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Vladlen Sirotkin, 11/1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Sergei Smolnikov, 10/1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Andrei Tsigankov, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Natalia Tsigankova, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Exchange Files on Exchange Participants: Galina Yemelianova, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - APSIA Exchange Questionaires, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - APSIA Exchange Protocol, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - APSIA Form Letters [1/2], undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - APSIA Deans and Liasons Officers, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - APSIA Funding, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Exchange Applicants: APSIA Exchange Questionaires, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - APSIA Exchange Protocol, undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - APSIA Form Letters [2/2], undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - APSIA Deans and Liasons Officers, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - APSIA Funding, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Exchange Applicants: Nancy Avera, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Exchange Applicants: Catherine Breen, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Exchange Applicants: Douglas Campbell, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Exchange Applicants: Eileen Crumm, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Exchange Applicants: Ronald Spector, undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Exchange Applicants: James Rosenau, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - APSIA/MFA Letter of Support/Intent, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - APSIA/MFA Early Official Documents, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - APSIA/MFA Visa Information, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - APSIA/MFA Conference, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - APSIA/MFA Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - APSIA/MFA Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - APSIA Applications and Related Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - IV World Congress (England), 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - International Research and Exchange Board Selection Committee, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - International Research and Exchange Board Short Term Grants, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - National Council, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dean East, 02/1989-06/1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Dean East, 07/1990-03/1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - SIP Conference: Beijing, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Wilson Center/Blitzer, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - MGIMO Business School, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Committee to Review Conflict of Interest Implementation, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Course Evaluation, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Symposium on the Soviet Millitary in 2010, 05/1990-06/1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Conference: 20th Century Russia-Germany in Comparative Perspective, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Rosemary O'Neill, Department of State: Training Program, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Affairs Assistance Corps, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Columbia University, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - CIA Course, 05/13/1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee on Indirect Cost Recovery Allocation, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Associate Dean [1/2], 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Associate Dean [2/2], 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Twentieth Sino-American Conference on Contemporary China, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Workshop: Reform in Soviet Union, Eastern Europe, and China, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Oklahoma: S/EP, 01/22/1992-26/1992 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Diplomacy Study: Working group at Georgetown [1/2], 1992 (Box 16, Folder 24)